Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Office Files, 1974
  - Government: Rail Passenger Service Act - AMTRAK, Civil Actions, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, Burlington Northern Railroad - Secretary of Labor Civil Action Nos. 825-71, 842-71, 843-71Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, Burlington Northern Railroad. Secretary of Labor Civil Action Nos. 825-71, 842-71, 843-71.
  - Government: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Government: President's Committee on the Physically Handicapped, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    Newsletters.
  - Government: Equal Employment Opportunity Commission - Charges (Houston Belt and Terminal Railway), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    CRU File. Includes correspondence and circulars in re gender equality in pay and in re racial discrimination by carriers and railroad labor unions.
  - Government: U.S. Railway Association (General), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    CRU File. Includes Annual Report of USRA through October 1974.
  - Government: U.S. Railway Association - Applicants, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Government: Court Cases (General) (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Government: Judicial - United States vs. Florida East Coast Railway, 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    CRU File. Case in re non- operating crafts strike. Also includes briefs from the Jackson Terminal Co. civil rights suit.
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (AMTRAK), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Includes circulars, 1974 All America Schedule, and arbitration awards.
  - Government: National Railroad Passenger Corporation (C-2 Protective Agreement), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Government: Civil Rights, General, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    CRU File. Includes draft of "Twenty Years After Brown: Equality of Educational Opportunity," a report of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights.
  - Government: United States Railway Association [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1a)
    Includes Annual Report of USRA through October 1974, Also includes bulletins and news releases in re implementation of regional rail reorganization.
  - Government: United States Railway Association [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1b)
  - Judicial: Court Cases (General), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Correspondence in re civil rights cases and in re the Burlington Northern merger's affect on employee protection agreements.
  - Judicial: Penn Central Bankruptcy and Reorganization, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Circulars in re the reorganization of Penn Central and its subsidiaries.
  - Judicial: Boston and Maine Reorganization, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Judicial: Lehigh Valley Reorganization, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Includes reports on the reorganization of the Lehigh Valley and its subsidiaries, including payment of back wages to employees.
  - Judicial: Reading Railroad Reorganization (United States District Court, Eastern District, Pennsylvania Number 71-828), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Brief filed by RLEA in support of reorganization of the debtor.
  - Judicial: Central Railroad Company of New Jersey Reorganization - United States District Court New Jersey Number B 401-67, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Includes circulars in re payment of back wages to employees.
  - Judicial: Jacksonville Terminal (Civil Rights), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Judicial: Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Reorganization, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Includes circulars in re the dissolution of the Merger protection Agreement and briefs filed by RLEA to compel the continuation of passenger train service.
  - Judicial: Joel Anderson and Prince Edmunds et al versus Southern Pacific Transportation Company Civil Rights, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Judicial: Regional Rail Reorganization Act of 1973 - Proposed Interim Abandonments Under Section 304(f), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Dockets of abandonments of Penn Central tracks.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: RLEA, General, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Includes Agenda item in re the reunification of RLEA and CRU.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Constitution and By-Laws, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Officers and Members, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Railway Supervisors' Association, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Includes announcement of a strike on the LIRR.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Information pack on 1974 National Rules Movement.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of the United States and Canada, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: By-Laws, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    CRU File. Signed by the five unions that withdrew from RLEA; TWU is not a signatory on these By-Laws.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Officers and Members, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Proposed New Regulations on Food Service Sanitation and Related Correspondence, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Seafarers' International Union, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Transport Workers Union: General and Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: United Transportation Union: General and Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Returned Questionnaires Regarding Congress of Railway Union Documents, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: CRU, General, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Meeting, Reservations, Etcetera, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    CRU File. Includes planning documents, agendas, hotel reservations, and hotel brochures.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Agendas, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Agenda Items, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    CRU File. Clipping from Business Insider in re the dissolution of The Rock Island properties in merger proceedings.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Minutes, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Insurance (General), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Office Policy: Traveler's Indemnity Company (Bowie Insurance Company), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Bowie Insurance Agency: Insurance Workmen's Compensation and Employer Liability Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: American Home Assurance Company (Policy Number 9900435), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Health and Welfare, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    CRU File. Travelers' Insurance group policies.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Railway Labor Building: Meetings, Etcetera, 1970-1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    CRU File. Financial reports and By-Laws.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Railway Labor Building, Lease, 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Committees (General), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    Includes Section 6 notice.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railway Employees' Department, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    Includes circulars and Awards from the Special Board of Adjustment.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Meeting, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    Includes planning documents, letters of invitation, and hotel brochures.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Meetings, General, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    Includes hotel promotional materials, planning documents, and correspondence.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Miami Meeting of Railway Labor Executives Association, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    Correspondence and hotel brochures.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Miami Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Meetings, General, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    Meeting schedules and hotel brochures.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Agendas, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Reports of Counsel, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    Includes updates on the reorganization proceedings of the Northeast carriers.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Assessments, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Applications for Affiliation, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Wages and Rules (General), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Radio Telephone Equipment Communications, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    Includes reports on use of Voice Train Control System.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Florida East Coast Railway, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    In re disbursement of funds post court decision.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedures, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1970 Wage Rules Movement, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1973 Wage Rules Movement - RED, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1973 Guaranteed Annual Wage - employee Security, Wages, Vacation, Holidays, and Rules Movement - Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1974 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Health and Welfare, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    Travelers' Insurance group policies.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers' Insurance Company [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1a)
    Group insurance policy
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers' Insurance Company [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Operating Unions, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Rules Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Shop - General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Dues - General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Task Force on Terminals, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Includes minutes of meetings and reports by the committee on intermodal networks.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Task Force - Terminals (Labor Management Meeting) [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8a)
    CRU File. Includes minutes of meetings, agendas, budgets for committee studies, correspondence, proposals for studies, and reports.
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Task Force - Terminals (Labor Management Meeting) [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8b)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Labor-Management Committee Meetings (CRU and AAR) [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9a)
    CRU File. Includes newspaper clippings, minutes of meetings, circulars, agendas
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Labor-Management Committee Meetings (CRU and AAR) [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9b)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Labor-Management, Terminals Task Force, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Wages and Rules Movement, General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Railway Labor Act, General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Railway Labor Act Section 6 Notice: Wage, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Railway Labor Act Section 6 Notice: Health and Welfare, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Strikes, General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Washington Job Protection Agreement, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Washington Jobs Protection Agreement of May 1936, Section 13 Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Washington Jobs Protection Agreement of May 1936, Docket Number 172, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: Washington Job Protection Agreement, Docket 130, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railway Labor Building, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committees (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Safety Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, etcetera, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with American Association of Railroads - Railroad L-M Relations [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 25a)
    Includes records from the Task Force on Terminals team, minutes of meetings, a petition to the ICC to increase freight rates, and circulars.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with American Association of Railroads - Railroad L-M Relations [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 25b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement (Tier 1 and 2 Informative Papers), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Includes analysis of proposed amendments to Railroad Retirement Bill.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on "C.O.A.L." Council of Allied Labor Burlington Northern, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Passes, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Personnel Records (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Protective Employees (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: GPO Account Number 11256, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Insurance (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Postage Meter, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Office Equipment (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: The XEROX Copying Machine, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Office Furniture (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 45a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 45b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers Bills, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Shop Crafts Dispute, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Contracting Out (General), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Railroads: General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Railroads: Ownership, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Railroads: Penn Central Reorganization, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Railroads: Auto-Train Corporation, 1970-1973 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Railroads: Erie-Lackawanna Railroad - Employee Protection, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    CRU File. Filings by CRU for enforcement of Employee Protection Agreements.
  - Railroads: Central Railroad Company of New Jersey - Reorganization, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    CRU File. In re payment of overdue wages.
  - Railroads: Litigation - Louisville and Nashville versus Interstate Commerce Commission et al, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Railroads: American Association of Railroads, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    CRU File. Statistical data sheets
  - Railroads: Reorganization of Reading Company, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Railroads: American Association of Railroads - Railroad Material Prices and Wage Rates, Quarterly Reports, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Railroads: American Association of Railroads - "Trends", 1974 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    CRU File. Newsletter
  - Railroads: Carriers Conference Committees, General, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Railroads: General, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Railroads: Railroad Ownership, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Railroads: Penn Central, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Railroads: Auto-Train Corporation, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6a)
    "Trends" newsletters.
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads (AAR) [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 15, Folder 6b)
  - Railroads: Western Railroad Association, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Notices of staff appointments.
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees (General), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations - Medicare, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO - General) [folder 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12a)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO - General) [folder 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12b)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO - General), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees - National Railway Labor Conference, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Other Organizations: Civil Rights, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Other Organizations: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations - Minutes, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Legislative Action Bulletin (Newsletter), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Legislative Council, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Executive Council, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Statements
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous and General, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Other Organizations: Research Institute of America - Recommendations, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Other Organizations: The Labor Management Committee for Fair Foreign Competition, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper - Financial Statements [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 27a)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper - Financial Statements [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 27b)
  - Other Organizations: Charities (General), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper - Special Editions, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, Incorporated., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - International Affairs: ITF, Amendments to the Address List, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    Financial reports and minutes of the annual meeting.
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of LABOR Newspaper, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: City of Hope, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - International Affairs: General, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs, 1970-1974 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    CRU File. Records of international railroaders visiting the United States.
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs - Foreign Visitors, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    Records of international railroaders visiting the United States.
  - International Affairs: Office of International Labor Affairs - Team Managers, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation (ITF), General, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    CRU File. Includes correspondence with international labor leaders, reports on conferences, reports on fact finding trips in various Central and South American nations, and bulletins.
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation - Constitution and Amendments, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation - Members (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation - Executive Board Members (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation - Caucus of United States Affiliates, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    CRU File. Held in New York City, July 25, 1974.
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation - Affiliation Fees, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 46)